[
	{
	  "category": "general",
	  "question": "What is the science that deals with the motion of projectiles",
	  "answer": "Ballistics"
	},
	{
	  "category": "historyholidays",
	  "question": "*Arnold Schwarzenegger made his film debut in 1974 In What Movie * ",
	  "answer": "*pumping Iron.*"
	},
	{
	  "category": "historyholidays",
	  "question": "\"Who invented the Christmas Cracker? (\"\"George Cracker\"\", \"\"Tom Smith\"\", \"\"Thomas Edison\"\", \"\"John Bell\"\" \" ",
	  "answer": "Tom Smith"
	},
	{
	  "category": "",
	  "question": "The old farming adage \"knee high by the fourth of July\" usually refers to the approximate height of what crop?",
	  "answer": "Corn"
	},
	{
	  "category": "general",
	  "question": "Where is the arch of hadrian",
	  "answer": "Athens"
	},
	{
	  "category": "general",
	  "question": "What does \"mit\"stand for",
	  "answer": "Massachusetts Institute Of Technology"
	},
	{
	  "category": "",
	  "question": "By definition,crostini is an Italian appetizer that requires what main ingredient?",
	  "answer": "Toasted Bread"
	},
	{
	  "category": "",
	  "question": "Influenza was named in the 15th century by Italians who believed it was caused by the influence of what?",
	  "answer": "Stars And Planets"
	},
	{
	  "category": "general",
	  "question": "This is the animal that never learns, \"Trix are for kids!\"",
	  "answer": "Rabbit"
	},
	{
	  "category": "general",
	  "question": "Old apothecaries weights 20 grains in a what",
	  "answer": "Scruple"
	}
  ]